export const data = {
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How would you describe your response to fearful situations?",
      "options": [
        "Calm and composed+0",
        "Occasionally uneasy+1",
        "Frequently anxious+2",
        "Overwhelming fear+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Calm and composed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you find yourself avoiding situations that trigger fear?",
      "options": [
        "Rarely or never+0",
        "Occasionally+1",
        "Frequently+2",
        "Always+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Rarely or never"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you experienced physical symptoms such as rapid heartbeat or sweating during fearful situations?",
      "options": [
        "Never+0",
        "Occasionally+1",
        "Frequently+2",
        "Always+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Never"
    },
    {
      "question": "How often do fearful thoughts impact your daily activities?",
      "options": [
        "Rarely or never+0",
        "Occasionally+1",
        "Frequently+2",
        "Constantly+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Rarely or never"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you feel a sense of dread or panic without an apparent cause?",
      "options": [
        "Never+0",
        "Occasionally+1",
        "Frequently+2",
        "Always+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Never"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you sought professional help or been diagnosed with a fear-related disorder, such as phobias or panic disorder?",
      "options": [
        "Yes+0",
        "Considering it+1",
        "No, not yet+2",
        "No, and I don't plan to+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Considering it"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you experience nightmares or disturbing thoughts related to fear?",
      "options": [
        "Never+0",
        "Occasionally+1",
        "Frequently+2",
        "Always+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Never"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have others expressed concern about your reactions to fearful situations?",
      "options": [
        "Never+0",
        "Rarely+1",
        "Sometimes+2",
        "Frequently+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Never"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you believe that addressing and managing fear-related issues is important for overall well-being?",
      "options": [
        "Strongly agree+0",
        "Agree+1",
        "Neutral+2",
        "Disagree+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Strongly agree"
    },
    {
      "question": "How would you rate the impact of fear on your daily life and activities?",
      "options": [
        "Low impact+0",
        "Moderate impact+1",
        "High impact+2",
        "Very high impact+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Low impact"
    }
  ]
}
